foreign
can drain you financially and
emotionally
with icicia Lombard health insurance you
no longer have to worry we can help ease
the financial burden while you focus on
getting better our health insurance
covers all medical expenses as per your
policy terms and conditions during
hospitalization
you can choose a partner hospital for
our convenient and easy cashless option
you can also choose a non-partner
hospital and follow our reimbursement
process if you have chosen to go through
the cashless process through one of our
6500 plus partner hospitals the steps to
follow are quick and easy at the
hospital third party assistant desk
submit your e-health card which is
available on our IL take care app or
with their policy document along with a
government-issued ID card the assistant
will then fill the claim form and take
care of the rest of the process for you
our team will assess your claim request
and share an update regarding your
cashless treatment within one hour of a
receipt of the claim well you can sit
back and receive your treatment in peace
at the time of discharge you only have
to pay the amount not covered in your
policy the rest of the amount will be
taken care of By Us in case you have
paid any deposit please coordinate with
the hospital for a refund
if you have chosen to receive treatment
at a non-partner hospital ICL Lombard
will process your vein within eight days
of registration
at the time of discharge you have to pay
the bill in full at the hospital and
remember to collect the required
documents
make sure to have your claim form fully
filled with the correct information
before you begin the reimbursement
process
submit your reimbursement claim through
the IL take care app or on WhatsApp the
easiest way to claim your reimbursement
is through ril take care app
login to Il take care app with your
registered mobile number
tap on claims and pick your policy
number in the menu tap on file a claim
simply fill in all the required details
in the next few screens
and upload the required self-addested
documents
[Music]
tap on submit your claim has now been
registered and will be cleared within
eight days
in the meantime you can check the status
of your claim on the IL take care app on
WhatsApp or on our website
[Music]
foreign
you can also claim your reimbursement
through WhatsApp
send us a high on the number shown on
screen and are responsive and
intelligent assistant Ria will assist
you through the reimbursement Journey
register your claim and pick your policy
number follow the process to enter the
information of your hospitalization
Maria will now prompt you to upload
self-attested documents which can be in
a PDF or jpeg format
this step your reimbursement claim is
registered and will be processed within
eight days of registration
in the meanwhile you can also track your
claim status on WhatsApp on the IL take
care app or on our website
you can also submit your claim for
reimbursement to us through registered
post or Courier mail in the original
hospitalization documents along with a
duly filled claim form to the address
shown on the screen
[Music]
with icicl Lombard health insurance
registering your health insurance claim
is simple and convenient
[Music]